{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Data and Digital Communications",
    "Term": "Finals",
    "Title": "Finals Reviewer",
    "LastModified": "15 December 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Finals Reviewer"
    ]
  },
  "quizData":[
    {
      "question": "In datagram networks, each packet may experience a wait at a switch before it is forwarded",
      "answer": "Delay",
      "choices": [
        "Delay",
        "Packet Loss",
        "Collision",
        "Error Detection"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "An information created and maintained by an organization that needed to be available to authorized entities",
      "answer": "Availability",
      "choices": [
        "Availability",
        "Security",
        "Integrity",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This wave propagation uses a low-frequency range transmission less than 1 MHz",
      "answer": "Ground Wave",
      "choices": [
        "Ground Wave",
        "Sky Wave",
        "Surface Wave",
        "Line of Sight"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the modulation technique in which the carrier frequency varies based on analog baseband",
      "answer": "Amplitude Modulation",
      "choices": [
        "Amplitude Modulation",
        "Frequency Modulation",
        "Phase Modulation",
        "Pulse Modulation"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This simple approach of error detection involves adding repeating bits to each character known as parity bits",
      "answer": "Vertical Redundancy Check",
      "choices": [
        "Vertical Redundancy Check",
        "Checksum",
        "Cyclic Redundancy Checksum",
        "Forward Error Correction"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This protocol's primary function is to turn an unreliable network into a reliable network that is free from lost and duplicate packets",
      "answer": "Transmission Control Protocol",
      "choices": [
        "Transmission Control Protocol",
        "User Datagram Protocol",
        "Internet Protocol",
        "Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a study of cryptography and cryptoanalysis",
      "answer": "Cryptology",
      "choices": [
        "Cryptology",
        "Cryptography",
        "Cryptoanalysis",
        "Cryptosystem"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It revolutionized long-distance communication by sending electric signals in Morse Code in between two stations",
      "answer": "Telegraph",
      "choices": [
        "Telegraph",
        "Telephone",
        "Internet",
        "Radio"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It refers to the loss of energy as signal propagates outwards",
      "answer": "Attenuation",
      "choices": [
        "Attenuation",
        "Amplification",
        "Reflection",
        "Refraction"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It provides a connectionless data transfer service over heterogeneous networks by passing through and routing datagrams",
      "answer": "Internet Protocol",
      "choices": [
        "Internet Protocol",
        "Transmission Control Protocol",
        "Network Access Protocol",
        "Internet Control Message Protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the art of creating and using cryptosystems",
      "answer": "Cryptography",
      "choices": [
        "Cryptography",
        "Cryptology",
        "Encryption",
        "Decryption"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This method treats each data packet as a big polynomial, adding 8 to 32 check bits to large data packets",
      "answer": "Cyclic Redundancy Checksum",
      "choices": [
        "Cyclic Redundancy Checksum",
        "Vertical Redundancy Check",
        "Parity Check",
        "Hashing"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a logic function used in cyclic redundancy checksum",
      "answer": "XOR",
      "choices": [
        "XOR",
        "AND",
        "OR",
        "NOT"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    }
  ]
}